Ladies' night at the Cheesecake Factory,
does it get any better than this?
(Penny:)I hope so.
Question: Do you think your husband's
fondness for turtle-necks...
(Amy:)...is an expression of longing
for his missing foreskin?
(Penny:)It's not getting any better.
Oh, it's Leonard.
He wants to go costume shopping later.
- I thought you liked Halloween.
- I do...
...he wants to go party at the comic store.
Lot of the guys there are kind of creepy.
- Like my husband?
- And my boyfriend?
(Penny:)I'm sorry, Amy, you were saying something
about Howard's foreskin?
(Bernadette:)Nice try, but you have to go to
that party because we're going.
(Penny:)I'm gonna go, it's just not my idea
of a good time.
Leonard does things he doesn't like
to make you happy.
(Penny:)Yeah, he's my boyfriend.
Isn't that, like, his job?